quiz_data = [
    {
        "question": "What is the brawler that came out in season 2?",
        "choices": ["Gale", "Surge", "Colette", "Lou"],
        "answer": "Surge"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the health of Nita's bear?(Level 11)",
        "choices": ["8700", "8400", "8000", "8600"],
        "answer": "8600"
    },
    {
        "question": "How many brawlers are there in brawl stars Season 29",
        "choices": ["100", "82", "74", "78"],
        "answer": "82"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Clancy's mastery title?",
        "choices": ["Shell Shock!", "Shell Shocked!", "Shell Shocking!", "Shell Shocker!"],
        "answer": "Shell Shocked!",
    },
    {  
        "question": "How many trophies do you need to finish trophie road in brawl stars?",
        "choices": ["40000", "50000", "60000", "70000"],
        "answer": "70000",
    },
    {
        "question": "What brawler has the gadget name 'Extra Sticky'?",
        "choices": ["Crow", "Mandy", "Barley", "Bibi"],
        "answer": "Bibi",
    },
    {
        "question": "What brawler has the Star power name 'Extra toxic'?",
        "choices": ["Byron", "willow", "Crow", "Cordelius"],
        "answer": "Crow",
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is the quote, 'Nerf ____', talking about?",
        "choices": ["lily", "Surge", "Clancy", "Poco"],
        "answer": "Poco",
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is foul mouthed in brawl stars?",
        "choices": ["Edgar", "Crow", "Jacky", "Bull"],
        "answer": "Jacky",
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is Jessie's parent?",
        "choices": ["Chester", "Janet", "Pam", "Colt"],
        "answer": "Pam",
    },
    {
        "question": "Who has the star power 'sponge'?",
        "choices": ["Doug", "Frank", "Darryl", "El Primo"],
        "answer": "Frank",
    },
    {
        "question": "Who is among the first set of characters to get a hypercharge?",
        "choices": ["Spike", "Jessie", "El Primo", "Nita"],
        "answer": "Spike",
    },
    {
        "question": "What brawl stars E-sport team won the world finals 2023?",
        "choices": ["Crazy Racoons", "Tribe Gaming", "STMN Esports", "Zeta Division"],
        "answer": "Zeta Division",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the fastest brawler in brawl stars?",
        "choices": ["Crow", "Max", "Colt with Star power", "Clancy"],
        "answer": "Clancy",
    },
    {
        "question": "How much damage does hanks fully charged bubble do at lv 11?",
        "choices": ["4000", "4200", "4400", "4500"],
        "answer": "4200",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the range of mandy's super in tiles?",
        "choices": ["30", "40", "50", "Infinite"],
        "answer": "40",
    },
    {
        "question": "What brawler has the most skins in season 29?",
        "choices": ["El-primo", "Colt", "Shelly", "Spike"],
        "answer": "Colt",
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of these brawlers did not have a mutation?",
        "choices": ["Surge", "Brock", "Kit", "Poco"],
        "answer": "Kit",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the name of Megs Mecha?",
        "choices": ["Rob", "Meg-a", "Mech 2.0", "It has no name"],
        "answer": "Rob",
    },
    {
        "question": "How many bullets does Meg shoot?",
        "choices": ["12", "16", "20", "24"],
        "answer": "16",
    },
    {
        "question": "What was the last brawler you could get from trophie road before it got deleted?",
        "choices": ["Stu", "Emz", "8-bit", "Bo"],
        "answer": "Stu",
    },
    {
        "question": "What country banned brawl stars?",
        "choices": ["Taiwan", "Veitnam", "China", "Russia"],
        "answer": "Veitnam",
    },
    {
        "question": "How many hypercharges are there in brawl stars season 29?",
        "choices": ["33", "42", "36", "37"],
        "answer": "37",
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the range of hank's super?",
        "choices": ["20", "30", "50", "Infinite"],
        "answer": "20",
    },
    {
        "question": "How many female brawlers are there (including female robot brawlers)?",
        "choices": ["27", "30", "34", "41"],
        "answer": "30",
    },
]